

TOMMY WALSH

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT STUDENT

CONTACT |





46 Waterloo Road, Ballsbridge, Dublin 4



tommywalsh1984@gmail.com



0851090243



My name is Tommy Walsh (Tomás Breathnach as Gaeilge) and I hail from a wee Fishing Village on the West Coast of Ireland. Being from the coast I do love the sea; however, technology has always had a special place in my heart. Much like my love for the sea, technology is something that enables a distinct lack of time comprehension. I just lose myself in the problem solving of it all.

I am living in Dublin since 2015 where after some extremely adventurous 18 months in the Sales and Marketing industry filled with many personal and professional firsts, I am delighted to say I am now pursuing my dream of a career in the ICT Industry by means of a Full Stack Diploma in Web Development with Code Institute. Extremely excited to take this step towards a new career in an industry that just keeps growing and growing.

On a personal note I love the outdoors especially taking wee walks along the coast when back home in Clare. My springer spaniel companion Buddy is always keen to stretch my legs. I have recently been bitten by the travel bug and although little over a year ago I was passport-less I have been lucky enough to visit Finland, Switzerland, Spain and Italy in the past 12 months. This helped me indulge in another personal love...food!! Whether cooking myself or trying somewhere new I love my food. Add in a healthy obsession for my laptop and that's pretty much the basics of what makes me, me!











TOMMY WALSH

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT STUDENT

SKILLS 🐣



Microsoft Office



Teamwork



Troubleshooting



Customer Service



Computer Repair



Currently Studying



HTML



CSS



12

Python

EDUCATION

- Diploma in Microsoft Excel
 Programming Foundations:
 Fundamentals
- HTML Fundamentals
- CSS Fundamentals

CERTIFICATES

- JS Tutorial
- Python 3 <u>Tutorial</u>

EXPERIENCE ____

ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE • FMI • 21-05-2017 -- 27-07-2017

Responsible for the day to day running of three high profile accounts, Nespresso, Canon and Unilever Pharma. Managed wages and rosters for over 40 staff members over the three accounts.

CONTACT CENTER REPRESENTATIVE • FMI • 17-02-2016 -- 21-05-2017

During my time at FMI I worked on many accounts in various industries from the Electricity Market to Hotel Reporting.

My main daily duties involved contacting customers over the phone. I was also tasked with inputting various data using different systems from Excel to BXP and CRM systems. This part of the role I enjoyed the most.

On a weekly, Monthly and Quarterly basis I created reports on some of the accounts I worked on which improved my Excel and PowerPoint skills immensely culminating in the completion of a Diploma in Microsoft Excel. During my time at FMI I received extensive training in various forms of data

During my time at FMI I received extensive training in various forms o entry, reporting, sales and customer service.

Very proud of getting the chance to take lead on a small account which gave me the chance to prove my worth and eventually resulted in promotion.

FULL STACK DIPLOMA IN WEB DEVELOPMENT • CODE INSTITUTE • 26-09-2017 -- PRESENT

Currently studying this one-year course with the Code Institute and thoroughly enjoying the challenge thus far. Learning so much as is evident from the linked <u>Certificates. My GitHub account grows</u> as the course continues.

LEAVING CERTIFICATE • 2002 • ST JOSEPHS, KILKEE, CO. CLARE

JUNIOR CERTIFICATE • 2000 • ST JOSEPHS, KILKEE, CO. CLARE





